<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christmas on Christmas Card and gift</title>
    <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/categories/christmas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Christmas on Christmas Card and gift</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright 2021 [pictart.github.io/christmas-card](https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 16:56:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/categories/christmas/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>83  Motivational quotes mahatma gandhi for Christmas Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-mahatma-gandhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 16:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-mahatma-gandhi/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Quotes Mahatma Gandhi, Employing nonviolent civil disobedience Gandhi. Motivational Quotes Mahatma Gandhi. Mahatma Gandhi Indian Leader born on October 02 1869 died on January 30 1948.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>68 New Love breakup motivation quotes for </title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/love-breakup-motivation-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 16:36:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/love-breakup-motivation-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Love Breakup Motivation Quotes, Dont do this simply find excuses for them. My love bytes brings you some of the best positive inspirational breakup quotes and inspirational breakup sayings that you can contemplate and sms to your if you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>99  Let go motivational quotes for Happy New year</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/let-go-motivational-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 13:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/let-go-motivational-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Let Go Motivational Quotes, The Best Quotes about Letting Go The truth is unless you let go unless you forgive yourself unless you forgive the situation unless you realize that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>57 Back To School 25 motivational sales quotes for Thanksgiving Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/25-motivational-sales-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 13:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/25-motivational-sales-quotes/</guid>
      <description>25 Motivational Sales Quotes, Formal education will make you a living. Work is an inanimate thing and can be made lively and interesting only by injecting yourself into it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>81 New Happiness motivational quotes about life for Christmas Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/happiness-motivational-quotes-about-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 12:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/happiness-motivational-quotes-about-life/</guid>
      <description>Happiness Motivational Quotes About Life, How to Overcome the Fear of Public Speaking A Step-by-Step Guide 1. According to experts were built to display anxiety and to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>53 Back To School Hustle and motivate nipsey hussle quotes for Thanksgiving Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/hustle-and-motivate-nipsey-hussle-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 11:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/hustle-and-motivate-nipsey-hussle-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Hustle And Motivate Nipsey Hussle Quotes, Here are some of the most popular and motivational nipsey hussle quotes. Nipsey hussle quotes about love friends money family hustle will motivate you to achieve success in life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>56 Best Motivational quotes for forex traders for Thanksgiving Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-for-forex-traders/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 10:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-for-forex-traders/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Quotes For Forex Traders, Traders must keep pushing forward and a list of inspirational trading quotes can fuel the fire and serve as a great motivator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>72 New Pineapple motivational quotes for Christmas Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/pineapple-motivational-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 08:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/pineapple-motivational-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Pineapple Motivational Quotes,
Pineapple Quote Free Printable Chalkboard Art Quotes Chalkboard Art Art Quotes From pinterest.com
Read another article:
Motivational quotes about best friends Motivational pt quotes Motivational quote template Motivational quotes about achievement Motivational positive quotes about life</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>70 New Christian workout motivation quotes for Thanksgiving Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/christian-workout-motivation-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 03:38:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/christian-workout-motivation-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Christian Workout Motivation Quotes, Nov 28 2015 - Explore PaulPrisilla Fullens board Christian workout quotes on Pinterest. See more ideas about quotes christian workout quotes workout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>53 Back To School Motivational inspirational quotes for young men for Christmas Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-inspirational-quotes-for-young-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 20:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-inspirational-quotes-for-young-men/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Inspirational Quotes For Young Men, Discover and share Motivational Quotes For Young Men. Discover and share Inspirational Quotes For Young Men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>84 Back To School Positive motivational life quotes sayings for Christmas Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/positive-motivational-life-quotes-sayings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 18:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/positive-motivational-life-quotes-sayings/</guid>
      <description>Positive Motivational Life Quotes Sayings, Life is 10 what happens to us and 90 how we react to it Dennis P.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>56 Best Motivational quotes from african american leaders for </title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-from-african-american-leaders/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 17:09:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-from-african-american-leaders/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Quotes From African American Leaders, To learn more here are 21 inspiring quotes from some of the most successful African American entrepreneurs and leaders throughout history and today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>95 New Quotes about motivation and hard work for Thanksgiving Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/quotes-about-motivation-and-hard-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 12:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/quotes-about-motivation-and-hard-work/</guid>
      <description>Quotes About Motivation And Hard Work, Your work is going to fill a large part of your life and the only way to be truly satisfied is to do what you believe is great work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>89 Recomended Motivational quotes from bruce lee for Happy New year</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-from-bruce-lee/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 11:47:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-from-bruce-lee/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Quotes From Bruce Lee, Bruce Lee Quotes About Flowing Like Water. I wish neither to possess nor to be possessed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>60 Recomended Motivational doctor who quotes for </title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-doctor-who-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 11:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-doctor-who-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Doctor Who Quotes, The hoper of far-flung hopes and the dreamer of improbable dreams 11th. Top 10 Inspiring Doctor Who Quotes I am and always will be the optimist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>58  Motivational prayer quotes for Happy New year</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-prayer-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 11:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-prayer-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Prayer Quotes,
Pin On Swell From pinterest.com
Read another article:
Best business motivational quotes Best hashtags for motivational quotes Best motivational baseball quotes Best hd wallpapers with motivational quotes Best life changing motivational quotes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>71  Fasting motivation quotes for Thanksgiving Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/fasting-motivation-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 11:04:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/fasting-motivation-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Fasting Motivation Quotes, Fasting Quotes - BrainyQuote The philosophy of fasting calls upon us to know ourselves to master ourselves and to discipline ourselves the better to free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>79  Motivational quotes images for success in hindi for Happy New year</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-images-for-success-in-hindi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 10:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-images-for-success-in-hindi/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Quotes Images For Success In Hindi, MOTIVATIONAL QUOTES IN HINDI FOR SUCCESS IMAGES. Motivational quotes in hindi for success 30 Motivational images in hindi 31 Positive Quotes in Hind 32 inspirational thoughts in Hindi 33 motivational quotes in hindi With Pictures 34 Best life quotes in Hindi 35 Best life quotes in Hindi 36 Motivational quotes in hindi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>91 Back To School Gangster motivational quotes for Christmas Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/gangster-motivational-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 10:52:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/gangster-motivational-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Gangster Motivational Quotes, Popular Juice Wrld Quotes Gangster quotes are interesting and speak about life love money friendship and loyalty in a hilarious manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>93 Best Motivational quotes monday funny for Happy New year</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-monday-funny/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 08:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-monday-funny/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Quotes Monday Funny, Monday morning it was all I hoped it would be John Phillips 10. Inspirational Funny Monday Motivation Quotes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>80 Recomended Motivational quotes to make you happy for Happy New year</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-to-make-you-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 07:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-to-make-you-happy/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Quotes To Make You Happy, A smile is the beauty of the soul. Its a good day to be happy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>61 Recomended Dhanush motivational quotes for </title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/dhanush-motivational-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 03:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/dhanush-motivational-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Dhanush Motivational Quotes, June 28 1983 It has been great journey from where I have started to where I am today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>81  American football motivational quotes for Christmas Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/american-football-motivational-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 02:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/american-football-motivational-quotes/</guid>
      <description>American Football Motivational Quotes, American Football Quotes The purpose of quoting Motivational Football Quotes for Athletes is to pump up confidence in them by helping them develop a clear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>91 Recomended Motivational senior quotes for Happy New year</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-senior-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 01:28:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-senior-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Senior Quotes,
44 Inspirational Graduationquotes With Images Inspirational Graduation Quotes Roosevelt Quotes Senior Quotes From pinterest.com
Read another article:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>94 Back To School Motivational quotes by chetan bhagat for Thanksgiving Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-by-chetan-bhagat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 01:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-by-chetan-bhagat/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Quotes By Chetan Bhagat, Chetan Bhagat Lets be honest. Author Screenwriter Banker Columnist Motivational Speaker Journalist Novelist From Five Point Someone to a reality show judge Chetan Bhagat is now a household name and has influenced many youngsters to follow their dream breaking the stereotype.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>88 Back To School Memorial day motivational quotes for </title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/memorial-day-motivational-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:49:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/memorial-day-motivational-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Memorial Day Motivational Quotes, Memorial Day Quotes for Brother. Inspiring Memorial Day Quotes for Veterans. I have long believed that sacrifice is the pinnacle of patriotism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>98 Top Motivational quotes from shakespeare for </title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-from-shakespeare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 19:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-from-shakespeare/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Quotes From Shakespeare, William Shakespeare on Self Love Self-love my liege is not so vile a sin as self-neglecting William.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>70  Positive motivational quote good morning thursday for Thanksgiving Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/positive-motivational-quote-good-morning-thursday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 13:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/positive-motivational-quote-good-morning-thursday/</guid>
      <description>Positive Motivational Quote Good Morning Thursday, Discover and share Thursday Morning Motivational Quotes. Explore our collection of motivational and famous quotes by authors you know and love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>69 Top Deep motivational love quotes for Thanksgiving Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/deep-motivational-love-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 12:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/deep-motivational-love-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Deep Motivational Love Quotes, It has the ability to change the world make or mar humans. You have found true love when you realize that you want to wake up beside your love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>83 Recomended Breakup motivation quotes for Thanksgiving Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/breakup-motivation-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 11:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/breakup-motivation-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Breakup Motivation Quotes, Here some best Quotes. But we often look so long and so regretfully upon the closed door that we do not see the one which.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>