<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>holiday on Christmas Card and gift</title>
    <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/tags/holiday/</link>
    <description>Recent content in holiday on Christmas Card and gift</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright 2021 [pictart.github.io/christmas-card](https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 16:56:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/tags/holiday/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>83  Motivational quotes mahatma gandhi for Christmas Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-mahatma-gandhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 16:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-mahatma-gandhi/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Quotes Mahatma Gandhi, Employing nonviolent civil disobedience Gandhi. Motivational Quotes Mahatma Gandhi. Mahatma Gandhi Indian Leader born on October 02 1869 died on January 30 1948.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>99  Let go motivational quotes for Happy New year</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/let-go-motivational-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 13:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/let-go-motivational-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Let Go Motivational Quotes, The Best Quotes about Letting Go The truth is unless you let go unless you forgive yourself unless you forgive the situation unless you realize that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>57 Back To School 25 motivational sales quotes for Thanksgiving Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/25-motivational-sales-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 13:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/25-motivational-sales-quotes/</guid>
      <description>25 Motivational Sales Quotes, Formal education will make you a living. Work is an inanimate thing and can be made lively and interesting only by injecting yourself into it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>79  Keep calm motivational quotes for </title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/keep-calm-motivational-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 07:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/keep-calm-motivational-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Keep Calm Motivational Quotes, When you are angry try your best to go to sleep it keeps you away from. Inspirational Keep Calm Quotes about Life and Serenity 21.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>60 Best Best quotes to stay motivated for Christmas Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/best-quotes-to-stay-motivated/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 04:46:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/best-quotes-to-stay-motivated/</guid>
      <description>Best Quotes To Stay Motivated, We hope you find a few you like and can revisit often to stay motivated. That said here are a few of our favorite motivational and inspiring quotes from a wide variety of sources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>79 New Motivational quotes suits for Thanksgiving Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-suits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 21:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-suits/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Quotes Suits, And form a new one that suits them better. Harvey Specter Suits Season 5. Anyone can do my job but no one can be me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>53 Back To School Motivational inspirational quotes for young men for Christmas Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-inspirational-quotes-for-young-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 20:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-inspirational-quotes-for-young-men/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Inspirational Quotes For Young Men, Discover and share Motivational Quotes For Young Men. Discover and share Inspirational Quotes For Young Men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>84 Back To School Positive motivational life quotes sayings for Christmas Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/positive-motivational-life-quotes-sayings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 18:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/positive-motivational-life-quotes-sayings/</guid>
      <description>Positive Motivational Life Quotes Sayings, Life is 10 what happens to us and 90 how we react to it Dennis P.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>84 Top Motivational quotes teamwork funny for </title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-teamwork-funny/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 17:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-teamwork-funny/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Quotes Teamwork Funny, This article contains 90 motivational teamwork quotes to inspire your team to strive for greatness. Funny Motivational Quotes Teamwork Funny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>92 Back To School Christmas motivational quotes for students for Christmas Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/christmas-motivational-quotes-for-students/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 17:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/christmas-motivational-quotes-for-students/</guid>
      <description>Christmas Motivational Quotes For Students, Our Team Designs Unique Items You Cant Find Anywhere Else. 101 Inspirational Christmas Messages and Quotes Here is a list of 101 inspirational Christmas messages and quotes to get them in the Christmas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>86 New Customer service week motivational quotes for </title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/customer-service-week-motivational-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 16:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/customer-service-week-motivational-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Customer Service Week Motivational Quotes, Courteous treatment will make a customer a walking. List 5 wise famous quotes about Customer Service Week Motivational.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>95 New Quotes about motivation and hard work for Thanksgiving Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/quotes-about-motivation-and-hard-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 12:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/quotes-about-motivation-and-hard-work/</guid>
      <description>Quotes About Motivation And Hard Work, Your work is going to fill a large part of your life and the only way to be truly satisfied is to do what you believe is great work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>58  Motivational prayer quotes for Happy New year</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-prayer-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 11:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-prayer-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Prayer Quotes,
Pin On Swell From pinterest.com
Read another article:
Best business motivational quotes Best hashtags for motivational quotes Best motivational baseball quotes Best hd wallpapers with motivational quotes Best life changing motivational quotes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>79  Motivational quotes images for success in hindi for Happy New year</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-images-for-success-in-hindi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 10:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-images-for-success-in-hindi/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Quotes Images For Success In Hindi, MOTIVATIONAL QUOTES IN HINDI FOR SUCCESS IMAGES. Motivational quotes in hindi for success 30 Motivational images in hindi 31 Positive Quotes in Hind 32 inspirational thoughts in Hindi 33 motivational quotes in hindi With Pictures 34 Best life quotes in Hindi 35 Best life quotes in Hindi 36 Motivational quotes in hindi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>97 Back To School Track motivational quotes for Happy New year</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/track-motivational-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 08:36:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/track-motivational-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Track Motivational Quotes, 20 Motivational Quotes to Keep You On Track. The shine has officially worn off many New Years resolutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>57 Back To School Nature motivational quotes for Thanksgiving Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/nature-motivational-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 08:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/nature-motivational-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Nature Motivational Quotes,
Old But Gold Nature Quotes Adventure Quotes Nature Quotes Inspirational From pinterest.com
Read another article:
Best motivational quotes after failure Best alone motivational quotes Best motivational coach quotes Best life quotes motivation Best 1 line motivational quotes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>93 Best Motivational quotes monday funny for Happy New year</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-monday-funny/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 08:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-monday-funny/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Quotes Monday Funny, Monday morning it was all I hoped it would be John Phillips 10. Inspirational Funny Monday Motivation Quotes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>81 Recomended Commerce motivational quotes for </title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/commerce-motivational-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 07:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/commerce-motivational-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Commerce Motivational Quotes, 200 favorite motivational quotes we hope you draw inspiration from as you continue through. Because shopping is a good time - like going to a nice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>94 Back To School Motivational quotes by chetan bhagat for Thanksgiving Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-by-chetan-bhagat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 01:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-by-chetan-bhagat/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Quotes By Chetan Bhagat, Chetan Bhagat Lets be honest. Author Screenwriter Banker Columnist Motivational Speaker Journalist Novelist From Five Point Someone to a reality show judge Chetan Bhagat is now a household name and has influenced many youngsters to follow their dream breaking the stereotype.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>57 New Network marketing motivational quotes in hindi for Christmas Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/network-marketing-motivational-quotes-in-hindi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 20:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/network-marketing-motivational-quotes-in-hindi/</guid>
      <description>Network Marketing Motivational Quotes In Hindi,
Business Motivation Network Marketing Quotes Motivation Strong Motivational Quotes Business Motivational Quotes From br.pinterest.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>92  Motivational quotes download pdf for Christmas Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-download-pdf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 10:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-download-pdf/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Quotes Download Pdf, 365 Daily Quotes for Inspired Living 1. Its only when you have the courage to step oﬀ the ledge that youll realize youve had wings all along.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>59  Parks and rec motivational quotes for </title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/parks-and-rec-motivational-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/parks-and-rec-motivational-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Parks And Rec Motivational Quotes,
10 Times Andy From Parks And Rec Was Every College Student Ever Parks And Rec Quotes Parks N Rec Senior Quotes From pinterest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>74 New Motivation to make money quotes for Happy New year</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivation-to-make-money-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 04:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivation-to-make-money-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Motivation To Make Money Quotes,
Pin On Dont Quit From pinterest.com
Read another article:
Motivational quotes trent shelton Motivational quotes whatsapp dp Motivational quotes with author name Motivational quotes wallpaper 4k Motivational quotes wallpapers hd 1080p for mobile</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>96 Recomended Motivational monday quotes fitness for Christmas Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-monday-quotes-fitness/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 02:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-monday-quotes-fitness/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Monday Quotes Fitness, 8 quotes to motivate you on Monday Its important to have strategies in place for the times you struggle to find motivation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>90 Best Motivational quotes tagalog version for Happy New year</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-tagalog-version/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 02:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-tagalog-version/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Quotes Tagalog Version, True love is a test of time. Best Motivational Tagalog Life Quotes. Inspirational Quotes About Love Tagalog Quotes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>68 Top Positive motivational business quotes for Thanksgiving Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/positive-motivational-business-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:28:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/positive-motivational-business-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Positive Motivational Business Quotes, And always be the hardest worker in the room -Dwayne The Rock Johnson entertainer. Business motivational quotes to inspire you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>81 Best Motivational inspirational quotes for life for </title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-inspirational-quotes-for-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 19:48:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-inspirational-quotes-for-life/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Inspirational Quotes For Life, As an example lets get the famous. You can talk with someone for years everyday and still it wont mean as much as what you can have when you sit in front of someone not saying a word yet you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>78 Best Motivational quotes wallpaper hd for mobile for </title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-wallpaper-hd-for-mobile/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 19:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-wallpaper-hd-for-mobile/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Quotes Wallpaper Hd For Mobile, Motivational quotes wallpaper hd for mobile. Jun 18 2019 - Motivational wallpapers with quotes for mobile which is the best motivation method we could follow since it is more convenient method of getting motivation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>80 Recomended Motivational quotes for giving birth for Thanksgiving Day</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-for-giving-birth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 18:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/motivational-quotes-for-giving-birth/</guid>
      <description>Motivational Quotes For Giving Birth, Just as a womans heart knows how and when to pump her lungs to inhale and her hand to pull back from fire so she knows when and how to give birth Virginia DiOrio From Your.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>77 Top My mom is my motivation quotes for Happy New year</title>
      <link>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/my-mom-is-my-motivation-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 17:23:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pictart.github.io/christmas-card/my-mom-is-my-motivation-quotes/</guid>
      <description>My Mom Is My Motivation Quotes,
Pin By Erica House On Things I Love Inspirational Quotes Life Quotes Quotes From pinterest.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>